# SARABJIT BANSAL

## FULL STACK DEVELOPER

#### **ABOUT**

I am a foodie, interior stylist and a full-stack developer with strong programming skills making a return to the IT industry after moving from overseas.

Having worked for almost 6 years in the IT industry has given me strong coding etiquette along with project management and communication skills. I have brought myself up-to-date with the latest in tech and am looking forward to an exciting future in IT.

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

## OPERATIONS MANAGER

Achieva Agents | Sep 2016 - Nov 2017

- · Creating and processing customer orders within SAP,
- Responding to enquiries from clients via phone and email,
- Running reports and updating consignment details in databases

#### PROPERTY STYLIST

Uplift Interiors | Jun 2015 - Aug 2016

- · Carrying out the installation of furniture and styling accessories,
- Managing admin work including quotations and invoices,
- Suggesting and integrating changes on the website

# SOCIAL MEDIA MARKETING INTERN

Learning Fever | Jan 2015 - May 2015

- Researched and produced recommendations report that contained innovative ideas for promoting the website,
- Carry out competitor analysis and find keywords for SEO

## SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

Modern Software LLC | Feb 2009 - Nov 2014

- Designed and developed custom Assets, Budgeting, Finance, Fleet, Inventory & Purchasing modules in VB6 and Visual Studio,
- · Carry out modification requests at client sites,
- Provided technical support and maintenance services

# EDUCATION

GENERAL ASSEMBLY Web Development Immersive Feb - May 2018

PUNJAB TECHNICAL UNIVERSITY Bachelor of Technology, Computer Science 2004-2008

#### **SKILLS**

HTML

CSS/SCCS

JavaScript, jQuery, AJAX, three.js React, Ruby on Rails PostgreSQL, SQL Git

Visual Studio, Visual Basic 6

#### CONTACT

P: 0432 854 277

E: sarabjit.bansal@gmail.com W: sarabjitbansal.github.io

## SOCIAL

linkedin.com/in/sarabjit-bansal github.com/SarabjitBansal

## **REFEREES**

Available on request